Dr. Jackson. Dr. Jackson.
You are wanted urgently in
emergency ward number 3.
Whose patient?
Mine, sir.
You're late.
Patient went into
shock in the OR.
So miraculous Dr. Jacobs
has saved yet another life.
Well, the surgeon needed help.
Spare me the heroic details.
Let's get on with this.
Yes, sir.
Mrs. Thatcher's BUN
level was elevated, so we...
Did you repeat the blood test?
No.
Why not?
We hydrated her
and she improved.
How do you know she improved
if you didn't repeat
the blood test?
Dr. Westlake, the
flow chart here shows...
I can't tell anything from this.
What I was going to say was...
In my 30 years of
practicing medicine,
I have never seen such a
sorry excuse for a resident team.
Jacobs doesn't know how
to do a proper diagnosis.
Shaw's here only
because of his father.
Jackson has a lame
excuse for everything.
And Campion can't tell a scalpel
from a toothbrush.
I'm wasting my time.
Sir, I'll explain if you
give me a chance.
Evaluations
come out in the
morning, gentlemen.
Have a nice day.
You too sir.
You don't really think he'll
give us bad evaluations, do you?
I think he's
capable of genocide,
given the right equipment.
He can't give all four
of us bad evaluations.
That wouldn't make
him look very good.
Well, you don't
seem too worried.
I'm not.
Well, that's because you're
demonstrably superior.
Don't bait me, Jacobs.
Save your personality
for the student nurses.
Listen, Jackson,
don't be so smug.
I happen to know Westlake
has given bad evaluations
to a resident team before.
And it's taken each
one of them years
before they got out
from under that cloud.
Dr. Radburn.
May I join you?
Have a seat.
Well, man, this is a
particularly grim group.
Dr. Westlake at it again?
How'd you know?
I've seen these symptoms before.
He's doing our
evaluations tonight.
I gotta go to work.
Me too.
Say, could you give me a
ride home in about an hour?
I may hang around a
while. Can you wait?
Mm. Nah, that's okay.
I'll get one with Sean.
So, uh, how bad is it?
I think I pushed my luck
a little too far with
Westlake this time.
Why don't you talk to him?
Couldn't hurt.
Yeah, maybe I'll talk to him.
Later.
Dr. Westlake, I know you're...
Oh, man.
I can't believe it.
When did it happen?
Sometime during the night.
The janitor found his body.
Looks like we
got lucky after all.
What's going on?
Westlake's been murdered.
Make way, folks. Coming through.
God.
Man.
I think I need some air.
X-ray technician on call,
please call the emergency room.
X-ray technician, call
the emergency room.
How are you this
morning, Mrs. Wilson?
Better than you.
Oh?
I'm still in bed,
and you're up with the chickens.
Resting comfortably?
You're not Dr. Thomas.
No. No, I'm not.
I'm sorry.
I can't see a thing
without my glasses.
And I can't find them anywhere.
Dr. Hines, outside call.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I haven't seen you before.
I... I'm on a new rotation.
You stop by any time, young man.
Well, thank you.
I'll remember that. Thank you.
Bye.
Dr. Granville, please
call the operator.
Dr. Granville.
Bruce Jacobs?
Yeah?
I'm Lieutenant
Brooks, Atlanta P.D.
I'd like to ask you
a few questions.
Listen, I'm already late for
my morning rounds, lieutenant.
Well, this'll only
take a minute.
Uh, Dr. Jacobs, uh,
where were you
last night at 11 p.m.?
Last night I guess I
was home watching TV.
Alone?
Yes. Why?
What time did you
leave the hospital?
Around 10:00. Listen,
I... I really have to go.
You know, a security
guard saw you leaving
through a rear entrance
last night at 11:30.
Maybe I was wrong
about the time.
When was the last time
you saw Dr. Westlake?
About 9 a.m. For morning rounds.
You sure you didn't
see him after that?
Of course I'm sure.
We have an eyewitness
who can place you
in Westlake's office
at 11:00 last night.
I'm gonna need you to
come with me, Dr. Jacobs.
Bruce Jacobs?
The one and only.
Benjamin Matlock.
Norman Radburn's an
old friend of the family.
He says you need a good lawyer.
I need a great lawyer.
Well, I'm pretty good.
The police have this nurse,
Helena Richards, and
she says she saw you
going into Dr. Westlake's office
at the time of the murder.
Is that true?
I went to his
office to talk to him.
He was dead when I got there.
The story is that
you were afraid
of what he might
do to your future.
Well, that's why I
went to talk to him.
I was hoping we
could work things out.
The police found your
lab coat in your apartment
with the victim's blood on it.
It got stained when I
was checking his pulse.
Why did you lie to the police?
Because I was scared.
I put in eight years studying
to be a doctor, Mr. Matlock.
I ran, I panicked,
and then I lied.
I don't have an excuse.
Okay.
You're a resident
at the hospital, right?
Yeah, that's right, yeah.
That's like a doctor.
Yeah. More or less, yeah.
I've got this pain right here.
It comes and goes.
Well, have you been
for a physical lately?
Oh, no, no. Not for
a little thing like that.
It's not so bad in the morning.
Sometimes after
supper it hurts awful.
Could be gastroenteritis.
Gastritis.
That serious?
Well, it's hard to tell.
Look, Mr. Matlock,
level with me.
Have I got a chance here?
In the... In the old days,
when a person was really sick,
doctors used to
make house calls.
They'd come out and
thump you on the chest
and put things in your mouth
and ask you to say, "ah."
Sometimes they'd
know what was wrong
and sometimes they wouldn't.
And when they didn't,
they didn't say anything,
because they didn't want
you to know they didn't know.
Right. So you know
what they said?
"Take two aspirin and
call me in the morning."
Yeah, so I'll see
you in the morning.
Thanks. Thanks, Mr. Matlock.
Ben, I've known Bruce
Jacobs since he's 5 years old.
Mm.
I honestly don't think he
could do something like that.
Hm.
Did anybody else know
that Dr. Westlake
was up here that night?
Just the rest of
the resident team.
David was busy writing
up their evaluations.
None of them were
too happy about it,
I can tell you that.
You think one of them
might have done it?
Be hard-pressed to pick one.
Shaw... Shaw's father's
the top radiologist here.
Campion graduated
from Harvard, straight A's.
Jackson has an attitude problem,
but he's here under
a full scholarship.
Cream of the crop, huh?
You know, David told
me something yesterday
about investigating a theft.
Uh, the only thing he told
me is he's not gonna stop
until he gets to
the bottom of it.
Maybe he did.
I hope that's not my
heart. It sounds awful.
That's because you're
listening to your stomach.
Huh? Your stomach.
Oh.
Got a nice rhythm.
It's supposed to.
You know...
I developed a little
pain right there.
Just every now and then.
What do you think it might be?
Why don't you come
in for a full physical?
It's been a long time, Ben.
Oh, I don't wanna
go through all that
for just a little... Could
be your gallbladder.
Gallbladder?
You think so? Maybe.
Hm.
♪ Remember that rainy evenin' ♪
♪ I threw you out with nothi"
But a fine-toothed comb ♪
You dirty guy.
♪ I know that I'm to blame ♪
♪ Well, ain't that a shame ♪
♪ Bill Bailey Won't
you please come? ♪
♪ Bailey, won't
you Please come? ♪
♪ Bailey, won't you
Please come ho-o-o-ome? ♪
Ha-ha-ha.
Thank you. Yes.
I don't know what's better, Ray,
you and Bill Bailey
or the salmon.
Rip off a little
"Is You Is Or Is
You Ain't My Baby?"
Hello, Tyler.
Gents.
"Is You Is Or Is
You Ain't My Baby?"
Hell, no. I'm just
a guy you know.
You don't look good.
Where don't I look good?
You ever think about
taking a physical?
Now, you're sure
this isn't going to hurt?
Relax, Mr. Hudson.
People check in for
physicals every day.
Hey, I thought you said
this was a private room.
This is your new
roommate, Mr. Lipman.
How you doing?
"How am I doing?"
I'm in the hospital.
How do you think I'm doing?
Is he always this friendly?
Mr. Lipman is
one of our regulars.
Yeah.
I know you.
I saw your picture in the paper.
You're the eyewitness
to that murder.
The DA has asked
me not to talk about it.
Yeah, if you ask me,
it's the food here that
did that poor guy in.
All right, Mr. Hudson,
why don't you lie down and
make yourself comfortable.
Okay.
Dr. Hines, outside call.
How's that?
Just great.
Yeah, this isn't bad at all.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
Uh, may I?
Sure. Take a seat.
Ben Matlock.
I'm Bruce Jacobs' lawyer.
You're on his
resident team, right?
That's right.
Dr. Radburn says
that you're the most
promising doctor on that team.
I'm flattered.
It shouldn't come as a surprise.
I mean, you had that
scholarship to Harvard
and worked your way through
undergraduate
school, medical school.
I know something
about how that feels.
It's not easy.
No, it wasn't.
No.
You know, if, uh... If
I were in your shoes
and somebody was
threatening to ruin my future,
like Dr. Westlake,
I'd get pretty mad.
I hope you're not suggesting
what it sounds like
you're suggesting.
Oh, no, no, no.
Just an observation.
Of course, I will
have to ask you
where you were at
the time of the murder.
In my apartment.
Alone.
How'd you get there? I
heard you needed a ride.
I walked.
Oh.
Well, I guess that
takes care of that.
Um, a resident is
like a doctor, isn't he?
A resident is a doctor.
Well, I've got this pain,
it came on all of a sudden.
What do you suppose it could be?
At your age it could
be diverticulitis.
Herb. Yeah.
Uh, look, I'm telling you,
I got this guy in here,
serious peritonitis,
he's been delirious
for, like, six hours.
He keeps running off
about some takeover
at Waynebeck Industries.
I do some checking.
I find out this
guy's a stockbroker.
He... Herb.
Herb, listen to me.
You buy me 20,000 shares
of that stock immediately.
Dr. Granville,
please call the
operator. Dr. Granville.
Dr. Shaw?
Ben Matlock.
I'm Bruce Jacobs' lawyer.
You're on his
resident team, right?
That's right.
Hey.
Dr. Radburn says
that you're the most
promising member of that team.
Really?
Yeah.
It shouldn't come as a shock.
Uh, Sarah? Me.
Listen, have I got any...?
Okay, I'll hold.
I mean, your father says
you're a prominent surgeon,
your uncle's a doctor, your
grandfather was a doctor,
you got so many
doctors in your family
you can start your own hospital.
It gives you
something to live up to,
that's for sure.
I imagine the pressure
sometimes is immense.
I sure wouldn't want to
disappoint family like that.
How's...? How's the case going?
Uh... Uh...
Sarah? Listen, have
I got any mes...?
I'll hold.
Now, how's that?
How's the case going?
Oh, fair. Fair.
It, uh... It would help if
we knew which resident
actually killed Dr. Westlake.
You don't include
me in that, do you?
Oh, I have to.
You had ample motive,
unless, of course, you
can prove where you were
at the time of the murder.
I... I crashed in the doctor's
lounge, then I went home,
but I... I can't prove it.
Look,
I didn't have anything
to do with his murder.
Uh, yeah, Sarah?
Listen, uh, have
I got any mes...?
All right, I'll hold.
Dr. George Freeland,
please report to
the third floor...
Hey, doctor?
I've got a pain right there.
Right there? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
What do you think that could be?
I... There's some
stomach flu going around.
Wait. Sarah?
Listen, don't put
me on hold anymore.
Have I got any messages?
Who were all those calls for?
Give them Charlene's
number in Philadelphia.
Call my broker.
Tell him to sell
Waynebeck Industries.
Thanks, doctor.
Oh, what I wouldn't
give for a cup of java.
Restricted diet, huh?
"Restricted"?
Never in my life have
I seen gray chicken,
and I hope and I pray
I never see it again.
I've heard that before.
How long have you
been working here?
Eight years this May.
It's a living.
Security must be kind of a
tough problem in a place like this.
We run a pretty tight ship.
If anything was going
on, I'd know about it,
believe me.
Hey, that's a really nice
watch you got there, bud.
Yeah. It's the real thing too.
How can you tell?
Hey, come on. The imitations?
The second hand
doesn't sweep like that.
Must have set you back
at least 1,500 bucks.
I gotta go.
Hi.
Who are you?
I'm Ben Matlock,
Bruce Jacobs' lawyer.
I've been waiting for you. I
didn't wanna wake you up.
I know how hard you fellas work.
What do you want?
Well, I'm trying to
find out which resident
actually killed Dr. Westlake.
Police seem to
think Bruce Jacobs
did a good job of it.
Think he did?
I have no opinion.
Oh.
Dr. Radburn says that he thinks
you're the most promising
resident on the team.
I won't debate the point. Yeah.
He also says that you're
the most cold-blooded,
ambitious, potentially
ruthless doctor he's ever known.
I won't debate the point.
Hey, doctor,
I've got a pain right...
I don't give free advice.
Oh.
Oh!
God bless you.
Ben, you have no idea
how cold it was in there.
I'm lucky I didn't
get pneumonia.
I'm sorry. What happened?
God bless you.
Well, to begin with,
our friend Bernie
the security guard
wears a watch I
can't even afford.
Last night at 9:30,
two hours after he
got off from work,
I saw him open the research
lab and let a doctor in.
Did you see who it was?
At night all doctors
look the same in uniform.
All I saw was a white
jacket and white sneakers,
and then I got locked up.
God bless you.
What kind of research
do they do in the lab?
I don't know.
You don't feel like you
have a fever exactly.
I hate hospitals.
They are designed
to make you sick!
Don't get agitated.
Eat your lunch.
It doesn't look too bad,
except maybe
for that gray thing.
My friend might be
running a little temperature.
Now, we'll have you up
and out of here in no time.
Mm.
So, what goes on
in here, Dr. Lyden?
Well, we're developing
a new vaccine.
Oh?
Uh, anything you can talk about?
Well, at this point our
research is confidential.
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh.
You know, I... I read a
piece one time on a...
On a new drug, uh,
for... For baldness.
And it said that if a company
ever finds one that works,
it will be worth hundreds
of millions of dollars.
Is your vaccine worth
anything like that?
Well, if it works, yes.
Are you at the point
where your research
would be worth stealing?
Oh, yes.
Why?
Are you aware someone's been
sneaking into your laboratory?
How do you know that?
Well, at this point, my
research is confidential.
Actually, I knew someone
had accessed my computer.
How's that?
Well, I decided to do some
work at home one night last week,
and I tried to log
into one of my files,
but I couldn't get in
because the file
was already in use.
No one is supposed
to be in that file,
and I'm the only one
who can get in it by phone,
so I figured
someone was in here.
Oh.
What did you do?
Nothing much.
I assumed one of the residents
wanted to study my work,
so I notified Dr. Westlake
and left it at that.
When was this?
Well, I believe...
it was the night
he was murdered.
Now, let me understand this,
you're saying that someone
was stealing my research
and that's connected
to Dr. Westlake's death?
Like the chicken and
the egg, Dr. Lyden.
Only this time,
we know which one came first.
Oh, God.
What are you doing?
Checking out.
Why didn't you tell me what
that barium x-ray was like?
You didn't finish
your physical yet.
They're killing me!
I brought you these.
I thought they
might cheer you up.
You know, I felt great
when I checked in here.
I'm sorry.
I hate you for this.
I know.
But I think we finally have
a motive for this murder.
Dr. Westlake was not killed
because some resident
thought he was gonna
be dropped from the hospital.
He was killed because he
caught somebody stealing research
worth millions of dollars.
Did you talk to
the security guard?
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Well, he knows who's
been breaking in the lab.
But if I talk to him,
everybody will get suspicious.
Nurse Richards,
after Dr. Westlake
went into his office,
did you see anyone
else follow him in?
Yes, sir, I did.
And do you see that individual
here in the courtroom now?
Yes, I do. He's
seated right over there.
Indicating the defendant.
I saw Dr. Jacobs go
into Dr. Westlake's office,
and a few minutes later he left.
And after that did
you see anyone else
go in the office?
No, I didn't.
I was across the hall
for at least another hour.
No one else went
into that office.
No further questions.
Cross-examine?
Um, ahem, Miss Richards,
the way I hear
it, in a hospital,
doctors come and go,
but it's the nurses who really
take care of the patients.
Is that right?
Actually, yes.
That must be pretty tough,
on your feet eight
hours every day,
taking care of sick people,
crisis coming at you
one after another.
Must get pretty tiring.
Yes, sir. It does.
So you leave the hospital
right after your shift.
Yes, I do.
But... on the night
of the murder,
you didn't.
Now, how's that?
I had some paperwork
I had to complete.
Oh, yeah. That's why you were
in the office directly
across the hall
from Dr. Westlake's office.
Yes.
And you had a good view
into Dr. Westlake's office.
I mean, you weren't
down the hall.
I was right across
from his door.
Now, it was after 8:30 at night.
They usually turn down the
lights in the hall, don't they?
Yes, they do.
That must make it pretty dim.
Yes, it does.
Well, in that dim light, you
sure nobody slipped by you?
Yes, I am.
Now, in that dim
light of the hall,
you sure you saw Dr. Jacobs
go into Dr. Westlake's office?
Not really.
How did you identify him?
Well, I saw him when he came
out of Dr. Westlake's office.
Don't all residents
dress pretty much alike?
Pretty much.
So you saw a person coming
out of Dr. Westlake's office
wearing the usual dark
pants and white lab coat.
Dr. Jacobs was
wearing dark pants
and a lab coat, Mr. Matlock.
But in the dim
light of the hall,
if all residents dress
pretty much alike,
how can you be so
sure it was Dr. Jacobs?
I saw his face clearly in
the light from the office.
Mr. Matlock.
Uh, excuse me for a
moment, Your Honor.
Make it brief.
Mr. Matlock, she's lying.
I didn't have my lab coat
on when I left the office.
I got blood on
the sleeve inside,
so I took it off, I rolled
it up, and had it under
my arm when I left. Yeah?
Well, a security guard
saw me with it off.
The security guard wouldn't
know when you took it off.
Oh.
Uh, so excuse me, uh,
Miss Richards, let's see.
Where were we?
So
You saw a person coming
out of Dr. Westlake's office?
Not a person, Mr. Matlock.
Dr. Jacobs. MATLOCK:
Wearing dark pants
and carrying a white lab coat.
Is that right?
You're trying to
trick me, aren't you?
I'm an officer of this court.
I'd never try do
a thing like that.
He was wearing dark pants,
and he was wearing
a white lab coat.
And it was Dr. Jacobs.
Thank you, Miss Richards.
Your Honor, I reserve the right
to recall this witness.
That's all for now.
You examined the patient
when he was admitted?
Of course.
Didn't occur to you that
he might have pneumonia?
I was waiting for the
test results to come back.
In the meanwhile,
Mr. Sloane's temperature
jumped to 103.
Dr. Radburn, it's for you.
Will you please take a message?
Dr. Jackson,
sometimes we have to...
To go with our instincts.
Dr. Radburn, it's Dr. Lyden.
He says it's important.
Yes?
Oh, really?
Oh, that's wonderful.
I'll be right there.
Thank you.
Dr. Jackson.
Let us assume that
Mr. Sloane has pneumonia
unless the tests tell
us differently, okay?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Well, now, we know
who did it and why.
Yeah.
All we have to
do now is prove it.
We'll give it a shot.
Ben, I got to give it to you.
You are one sly old fox.
Well, I'll take that
as a compliment.
Please do. You
convinced that nurse
that there was a
breakthrough in the lab.
She calls her boyfriend
and bang-o, we
got ourselves a thief.
Well, it'll take more than that.
Somehow we've got to
tie our killer to this office.
Yeah.
Hm.
Mm.
Well, this don't sound so good.
You're listening
to your stomach.
Huh?
Your stomach. Oh.
Yeah. Now, that's better.
Oh, Tyler. What?
You're a genius.
Even when you don't
have the faintest idea
what you're doing,
you're a genius.
Connect me with
Dr. Radburn, please.
Your Honor,
the defense recalls
Helena Richards to the stand
and begs the court's
permission to examine
her eyewitness testimony
with a brief demonstration.
Very well.
I remind you, Miss Richards,
you're still under oath.
I understand.
Miss Richards, you
testified yesterday
that most residents dress alike.
Is that correct?
Yes, it is. You also said
that the lights in the hallway were
dimmed when you saw someone
come out of
Dr. Westlake's office.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Your Honor, at this time
we'd like the defendant
to leave the courtroom.
Your Honor,
what is the point of
this demonstration?
Your Honor, the
point will become clear
in another moment or two.
Go ahead, Dr. Jacobs.
Dr. Radburn of Chadway Hospital,
Your Honor, has
graciously agreed
to bring three residents
with him this morning.
They're all wearing
their white coats
and are dressed
exactly as they are
when they're working
at the hospital.
Now, Miss Richards,
you testified that
you saw the defendant
in the brief moment
that he stepped out
of Dr. Westlake's office
and went down the hall.
Is that correct? HELENA: Yes.
My associate, Mr. Hudson,
is gonna dim the
courtroom lights.
Just tell us when
the lights approximate
the way they were
in the hallway.
Mm-hm.
Okay, Tyler.
About there. Okay, Tyler. Fine.
Now, each of the residents
will come through
that back door,
walk across the back of
the room to that screen.
You should be able
to see each of them
approximately the
same amount of time
you saw the man come
out of Dr. Westlake's office.
Just tell us if you
recognize Dr. Jacobs.
You ready?
Mm-hm.
Okay, Tyler.
It wasn't him.
Next.
No. MATLOCK: Next.
That's him.
Turn up the lights, Tyler.
Your Honor, may
the record reflect
that Miss Richards once again
identified the
defendant, Dr. Jacobs?
So noted.
Mr. Matlock?
No further questions,
Your Honor.
Uh, just a moment, doctors.
Your Honor, the defense
calls Dr. Campion to the stand.
Dr. Campion, how long have
you known Helena Richards?
About three years, I guess.
We met when I came
to Chadway Hospital.
And how would you characterize
your relationship with her?
It was purely professional.
Do nurses usually
perjure themselves
for doctors with whom
they're having a purely
professional relationship?
Objection. Argumentative.
Assumes facts
not yet in evidence.
Sustained.
Dr. Campion, are you sure your
relationship with Nurse Richards
is purely professional?
We've socialized occasionally.
I think you're having an
intimate relationship with her.
That's why she testified
that she saw Dr. Jacobs
leaving Dr. Westlake's office
the night of the
murder, to protect you.
Relevancy, Your Honor.
I'm about to show the
relevancy, Your Honor.
Proceed.
You're a senior
resident, is that right?
Yes.
And soon you'll be
leaving Chadway Hospital
and going into private
practice. Is that right?
That's right.
It must be very expensive
to open an office.
Yes, it is.
Your Honor, at this time,
I'd like to introduce
into evidence
Defense Exhibit J.
These bank records of
Dr. Campion's savings account.
In the last several months
you've made several
healthy deposits, doctor,
for a person living
the life of a resident.
Your Honor, you know, I
don't see the point to this.
I'm coming to the point.
Proceed.
I think you were stealing
research from
Dr. Lyden's laboratory
and selling it to a
pharmaceutical company
for a lot of money.
That isn't true.
I'll tell you what
else I believe.
I believe Dr. Westlake
stumbled onto your thefts
and summoned you to his office,
and when he told you
he was gonna kick
you out of his hospital
and turn you over to
the police, you killed him.
That's a lie.
Doctor, you said you were at
home the night of the murder.
That's where I was.
And you said you were never
in Dr. Westlake's office
the night of the murder.
That's right.
You know, doctor,
I don't know a lot about, uh,
hospitals or... Or physicians,
but I...
I learned something
interesting yesterday.
I learned that
almost all doctors
and nurses at Chadway Hospital
purchase their stethoscopes
from the same hospital
supply company.
Is that right? Yeah, I guess so.
So there must be a lot
of people walking around
with identical stethoscopes.
Yeah.
I guess, uh, people pick up
the wrong one once in a while.
I suppose.
Well, I learned
that, uh, often times
doctors scratch their
initials or their name
or some identifying mark
on the back of
their stethoscope,
so it won't get mixed
up with somebody else's.
Is that right? Yes.
Do you have an identifying mark
on the back of your stethoscope?
My initials are on it.
Do you check it every
day to be sure it's yours?
Not usually.
It's always either
around my neck
or in my jacket pocket.
And no one ever
picks it up by mistake?
It's never happened.
I'm very careful.
You're sure that's
your stethoscope?
Yes.
Has the same fit and feel?
Doctor, I have a
confession to make.
I didn't really think
that little demonstration
that, uh, we put on
with Nurse Richards
was going to prove
that Dr. Jacobs
didn't kill Dr. Westlake.
But I did need you
to come down here
dressed as you are every
day with your stethoscope.
Would you read what's
etched on the back
of your stethoscope?
Read it.
"D.W."
D.W.
David Westlake.
Dr. David Westlake.
What are you doing
with that stethoscope?
I don't know.
I do.
In your struggle
with Dr. Westlake,
both stethoscopes fell,
and in your hurry to
leave after you killed him,
you picked up the wrong one.
No.
Do you recognize
this stethoscope?
This stethoscope was
found in Dr. Westlake's office.
And etched on the back is M.C.
Mark Campion, 1981.
No further questions.
Has the jury reached a verdict?
Yes, we have, Your Honor.
Defendant, please rise.
What is your verdict?
We find the defendant,
Bruce Jacobs, not guilty.
The not-guilty verdict
is entered into the record
and this court is adjourned.
Congratulations.
Thanks, Mr. Matlock.
Thank you so much.
Very nice work, Ben.
Oh, thanks.
I really enjoyed watching you.
Thanks.
Still bothering you, huh?
Well... You know,
by watching you,
I know what your problem is.
Yeah?
You're too fat.
Either lose weight
or get a bigger belt.
www.tvsubtitles.net